Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing Journal Submissions UA256
Tufts Archival Research Center
Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing Journal Submissions
circa 2020 -- 2021
Tufts Archival Research Center
Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College
UA256
1 Linear Feet 1 record carton
1197 Files
13.14 Gigabytes
679 Digital Object(s)
This collection contains submissions to ReSentencing Journal, a publication featuring creative work from prisoners across the United States, created by the Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College.
Content Description
This collection contains the submissions to the Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing literary journal. The records include submissions to the journal including stories, poems, essays, photographs, artwork, and letters from prisoners across the United States. The bulk of the material was created in 2021 for the 2022 edition of the ReSentencing journal and include both analog and digital submissions. In addition to the creative work submitted, many folders contain correspondence related to the submissions, often discussing the author's motivation to submit to the journal or contextual information about the submitter's life. Submissions may also contain information about the prisoner, including (not consistently) name, age, biographical date, address, prisoner number, sentencing and conviction details, phone numbers, email address, and information about their families.
Accruals
Further accruals are expected on an annual basis.
Arrangement
This series is arranged chronologically by date of accession.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) in June 2022, accession UA-2023-001.
Conditions Governing Access
Submissions to ReSentencing are open for research. All other records are restricted for twenty years from the date of creation of the record.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) responds to the problems of mass incarceration and racial injustice by connecting Tufts faculty and students with incarcerated and former incarcerated peoples. The program teaches a cohort of students at the MCI-Concord in a formal degree program. TUPIT also provides courses in a Civil Studies certificate program for people directly impacted by incarceration. The organization also connects students from the Tufts campus with students in prison and provides education to the Tufts campus community through symposia, speaking events, films, and exhibits.
The TUPIT program began in 2016 when director Hilary Binda created the college prison program with support of Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life and the University Office of the Provost. Binda established a partnership with the Massachusetts Department of Correction, to creating the degree behind bars program with partner school, Bunker Hill Community College. She created the Tufts Inside-Out course with the support of the MA DOC and Suffolk County facilities which connects students from the Tufts and prison campuses. The Degree Program expanded to include the Tufts Education Re-entry Network (TERN) and through this group developed MyTERN, a year-long certificate program in Civic Studies. MyTERN collaborates with community organizational partners such as Project Place, the Boston Mayor's Office of Returning Citizens, and Dorchester Bay Community Development Corporation.
Tupit's journal, ReSentencing, is an art and literary publication that includes poems, stories, essays, and visual art pieces created by current and formerly incarcerated individuals. TUPIT released its first edition of the ReSentencing Journal in August 2022. These creative works often, but not always, discusses the effects of the prison industrial and criminal justice systems on the artist. Some of the submitters have participated in a prison education program with TUPIT or another university. The submissions for the first journal were evaluated by established writers, artists, and scholars, some affiliated with NYU, MIT, Tufts, U Mass, and Yale. The ReSentencing advisory board includes Reginald Dwayne Betts, George Chochos, Michelle Daniel Jones, Helen Elaine Lee, Sandra Lim and ZZ Packer, among other artists and writers. The completed journal was sent to all contributors along with a small monetary compensation. Future editions of the journal are planned.
Prisoners -- United States; Tufts University Prison Initiative of Tisch College
- 2022 accessions, circa 2020 -- 2021; UA256.000001; 679 Digital Object(s)
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by name of submitter.
  - Ainooson, Justice, circa 2021; UA256.000002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Submissions to ReSentencing are open for research. All other records are restricted for 20 years from the date of creation of the record.
    Massachusetts; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Compassion / The Rhythm of Life, 2021 May 24; UA256.000003
      Open for research.
      Massachusetts; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Give us Freedom, 2021 May 24; UA256.000004
  - Akara, Chimezie, 2021 May 12; UA256.000005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Penance*, 2021 May 12; UA256.000006
    - Sacrilege: The End of An Era, 2021 May 12; UA256.000007
  - Alexander, Alana, circa 2021; UA256.000008
    Nebraska; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Love, Death, Life, & Regret, circa 2021; UA256.000009
      Nebraska; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Amara, Kareem Patrick Kwegor, 2020 July 30; UA256.000010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Black Supremacy, 2020 July 30; UA256.000011
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - You're Black Stop Talking White, 2020 July 30; UA256.000012
    - Nightmare on Elm St., 2020 July 30; UA256.000013
    - Stop Saying Nigga, 2020 July 30; UA256.000014
  - Anguille, Michael, 2021 June 8; UA256.000015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - For the Greater Good, 2021 June 8; UA256.000016
      Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
    - Dead Ends, 2021 June 8; UA256.000017; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
  - Applegate, Thomas, circa 2021; UA256.000018
    California; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - The Prison State, circa 2021; UA256.000019; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.78 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
  - Bailey, Quayshawn, 2021 June 29; UA256.000020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Can't you see, 2021 June 29; UA256.000021
      Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Broken, 2021 June 29; UA256.000022
  - Baker, Susan, 2021 May 24; UA256.000023
    Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Untitled essay, 2021 May 24; UA256.000024
      Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Banks, Jennifer, 2021 May 20; UA256.000025
    - Untitled essay, 2022 May 20; UA256.000026
  - Barker, Fred C., 2021 January; UA256.000027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Colorado; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Ballad of the Returning Citizen, 2021 January; UA256.000028; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
      Colorado; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Barry, Philip G., 2021 May 2; UA256.000029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    New York (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - The Visit, 2021 May 2; UA256.000030; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.07 Megabytes
      New York (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Baxter, David K., 2021 June 11; UA256.000031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lost & Found, 2021 June 11; UA256.000032; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.84 Megabytes
    - Loving a Convict, 2021 June 11; UA256.000033
    - Privilege & Power: America's Legacy of Racial Hate, Oppression, and Injustice, 2021 June 11; UA256.000034; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.97 Megabytes
      Massachusetts; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Beckham, Nicholas, circa 2021; UA256.000035
    - Three Little Words, circa 2021; UA256.000036
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Ghost, 2021 June 12; UA256.000037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - To Give To Grow, 2021 June 12; UA256.000038
    - Untitled visual art, 2021 June 12; UA256.000039; 1 Digital Object(s); 93.9 Megabytes
  - Bell, Calvin, III, circa 2021; UA256.000040
    Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Carcerality is Ubiquitous, circa 2021; UA256.000041
      Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Are You Truly FREE?, 2021 November 5; UA256.000042
      Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Dear Calvin, 2021 November 5; UA256.000043
      Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Bennington, Michelle, 2021 May 22; UA256.000044
    - Captivity, 2022 May 22; UA256.000045
  - Benton, George, 2021 May 26; UA256.000046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The band-aid tears of a scar fighting to be, 2021 May 26; UA256.000047
  - Berube, Crystal, 2021 June 25; UA256.000048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Rhode Island; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Existence, 2021 June 25; UA256.000049
      Rhode Island; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
  - Bey, Charles Anthony Jackson, 2021 May 24; UA256.000050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - I am, 2021 May 24; UA256.000051
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Prison Is, 2021 May 24; UA256.000052
    - Power, 2021 May 24; UA256.000053
    - Lost in the Mind, 2021 May 24; UA256.000054
  - Biggs, Christopher, 2019 -- 2021; UA256.000055
    - Who I am, 2019 June 22; UA256.000056
      Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - You gave me your word, 2019 June 22; UA256.000057
    - My Guardian Angel, 2019 June 22; UA256.000058
  - Bin, Peter, 2021 May 22; UA256.000059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A Mother's Love, 2021 May 22; UA256.000060; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.32 Megabytes
  - Bitton, Casey, 2021 April 27 -- 2021 May; UA256.000061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Utah; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Is it true?, 2021 April 27; UA256.000062
      Utah; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - If the Words I Write Could Paint Life, 2021 April 27; UA256.000063
    - The Diminished Capacity, 2021 April 27; UA256.000064
      Utah; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - To Assert, 2021 May; UA256.000065
  - Blango, Emmanuel, circa 2021; UA256.000066
    Connecticut; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Breaking Cycle, 2021 July 4; UA256.000067
      Connecticut; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Acceptance, 2021 July 4; UA256.000068
  - Blanton, Marcus, 2021 June 26; UA256.000069
    - Untitled essay, 2021 June 26; UA256.000070
  - Blazejowski, Towny, 2021 May 11; UA256.000071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - To My Precious Children, 2021 May 11; UA256.000072
    - I miss you, 2021 May 11; UA256.000073
  - Bolduc, Robert, 2021 June 17; UA256.000074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Flame visual art, 2022 June 17; UA256.000075; 1 Digital Object(s); 73.6 Megabytes
    - Flame visual art, 2023 June 17; UA256.000076; 1 Digital Object(s); 85.1 Megabytes
    - Heart and thorns visual art, 2024 June 17; UA256.000077; 1 Digital Object(s); 36.9 Megabytes
  - Bolling, Alexander, circa 2021; UA256.000078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Stormy Weather: Change and Compromise in America, circa 2021; UA256.000079; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.53 Megabytes
  - Bonds, Antonio, circa 2021; UA256.000080
    - Was Hustling worth Losing Everything, circa 2021; UA256.000081
    - Take Heed, circa 2021; UA256.000082
    - Love me, circa 2021; UA256.000083
    - Mug, circa 2021; UA256.000084
  - Ism, 2021 June 4; UA256.000085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Maryland; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - The Beginning, 2021 June 4; UA256.000086
      Maryland; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Duress, 2021 June 4; UA256.000087
    - One - to my son, 2021 June 4; UA256.000088
    - Beneficial, 2021 June 4; UA256.000089
    - A Thought, 2021 June 4; UA256.000090
    - Autobiography, 2021 June 4; UA256.000091
      Maryland; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Autobiography (genre)
  - Ra'sun Allah, 2021 May 1; UA256.000092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - A Diary of Reform, 2021 May 1; UA256.000093; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.90 Megabytes
  - Brantly, David, circa 2021; UA256.000094
    - A man cast adrift in a skiff hold his t-shirt…, circa 2021; UA256.000095
  - Brooks, Le'Mar N.D., circa 2021; UA256.000096
    - It's the end of the world and everyone's invited, circa 2021; UA256.000097; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.40 Megabytes
  - Brooks, Steve, 2021 July 1; UA256.000098
    - Finding wellness while in prison, 2021 July 1; UA256.000099
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Islamic Ali, 2021 June 11 -- 2021 September 23; UA256.000100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Until Islam is Recognized, 2021 September 23; UA256.000101; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.68 Megabytes
    - Textual visual art, 2021 June 11; UA256.000102
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
  - Brown, David, circa 2021; UA256.000103
    - Untitled short story, circa 2021; UA256.000104
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
    - Bird visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000105
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pastels (visual works)
    - Person and flame visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000106
  - XerXers!, circa 2021; UA256.000107
    - Untitled essay, circa 2021; UA256.000108
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Brown, Sandra, circa 2021; UA256.000109
    - Personal introduction, circa 2021; UA256.000110
      Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Autobiography (genre)
    - Labor Pains, circa 2021; UA256.000111
  - Bryant, John, circa 2021; UA256.000112
    - Untitled visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000113; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
  - Bryson, Christopher, 2021 July; UA256.000114; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - To Be Sorry, 2021 July; UA256.000115
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Alive Afterlife, 2021 July; UA256.000116
  - Butler, Katrina, circa 2021; UA256.000117
    - So far but so close, circa 2021; UA256.000118
    - What's in store for me???, circa 2021; UA256.000119
    - Free, circa 2021; UA256.000120
    - Maybe, circa 2021; UA256.000121
    - Grammatically Incorrect Life, circa 2021; UA256.000122
  - Buttner, John, circa 2021; UA256.000123
    Pennsylvania; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Identity, circa 2021; UA256.000124
      Pennsylvania; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
  - Camburn, Tracy Leigh, 2021 June 1; UA256.000125; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Gems, 2021 June 1; UA256.000126
    - The I Am Commemoration, 2021 June 1; UA256.000127
    - Not for Me, 2021 June 1; UA256.000128; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.64 Megabytes
    - Time Warp, 2021 June 1; UA256.000129
  - Campanella, Damian C., 2021 May 12; UA256.000130; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Precious Keepsakes, 2021 May 12; UA256.000131
      Connecticut; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Campbell, Kyle, 2021 June 21; UA256.000132; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Beyond Reimagining, 2021 June 21; UA256.000133; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.19 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Carter, James, 2020 March 1; UA256.000134
    - Using a token economy to prevent violence, 2020 March 1; UA256.000135
  - Carter, Travis, circa 2021; UA256.000136
    - Butterfly visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000137
    - Mushroom visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000138
    - Frog visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000139
  - Taye "Tha Sensei", 2021 May 25; UA256.000140; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - BLM - to WHO?, 2021 May 25; UA256.000141
    - Cartwright vs State of Tennessee, 2021 May 25; UA256.000142
    - Re-Imagine Incarceration, 2021 May 25; UA256.000143
  - Carver, Ashley, 2021 May 24; UA256.000144
    - Childhood, 2021 May 24; UA256.000145
    - Teenage Numb, 2021 May 24; UA256.000146
    - NOW, 2021 May 24; UA256.000147
  - Centrone, Jason, 2021 June 1; UA256.000148; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - The Bully Sibling: Aesopian Asininity, 2021 June 1; UA256.000149
  - Charriez, Christopher, circa 2021; UA256.000150
    - Locked in a cage for decades, circa 2021; UA256.000151
  - Chechobich, David, circa 2021; UA256.000152
    - Mushroom visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000153
  - Clark, Michael, circa 2021; UA256.000154
    - I know pain personally, circa 2021; UA256.000155
    - I am tired of walking these streets, circa 2021; UA256.000156
  - Clarke, Arnel, 2021 May 20; UA256.000157
    - Untitled essay, 2021 May 20; UA256.000158
      Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Clark, Gary, 2021 June 22; UA256.000159; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Lost Time, 2021 June 22; UA256.000160
      Connecticut; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - A Solitary Wonderland, 2021 June 22; UA256.000161
    - A Soul that Cries, 2021 June 22; UA256.000162; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.90 Megabytes
    - Four Walls, 2021 June 22; UA256.000163
  - Collins, Christopher S., 2021 May 12; UA256.000164; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - The Chameleon, 2021 May 12; UA256.000165
      Texas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Mania, 2021 May 12; UA256.000166
    - Calculated Risk, 2021 May 12; UA256.000167
    - Uncensored, 2021 May 12; UA256.000168
    - The final stages, 2021 May 12; UA256.000169
    - My hero, 2021 May 12; UA256.000170
    - The Puppeteer, 2021 May 12; UA256.000171
  - Cook, Abigail, circa 2021; UA256.000172
    - The Whimsical Sink, circa 2021; UA256.000173
    - Cardboard visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000174
      Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Sculpture (visual works)
    - Number portrait visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000175
      Georgia; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
  - Cooke, Exodus, 2021 May 15; UA256.000176; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Confused Peace, 2021 May 15; UA256.000177
    - A Cold Cruel World, 2021 May 15; UA256.000178
    - Penitentiary, 2021 May 15; UA256.000179
    - Framed, 2021 May 15; UA256.000180
    - Rejected by the Mirror, 2021 May 15; UA256.000181
  - Cooper, Jason, circa 2021; UA256.000182
    - Comic strip visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000183; 1 Digital Object(s); 25.3 Megabytes
  - Copeman, Jack S., 2021 May 24; UA256.000184; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Get a Mop, 2021 May 24; UA256.000185
    - Unrequited Paper Romance, 2021 May 24; UA256.000186
    - Notes From the Esophagus, 2021 May 24; UA256.000187
    - WHAT?! (patios), 2021 May 24; UA256.000188
    - Misanthrope, 2021 May 24; UA256.000189; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.67 Megabytes
    - State Blues, 2020 August; UA256.000944
    - MDOC Salad, circa 2021; UA256.000945
  - Cox, Alexander, 2021 June 8; UA256.000190; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Where did my childhood go?, 2021 June 8; UA256.000191; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.58 Megabytes
      Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - 16279332, 2021 June 8; UA256.000192; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.25 Megabytes
    - Out of the Furnace, 2021 June 8; UA256.000193; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.66 Megabytes
    - Concrete Vibes, 2021 June 8; UA256.000194; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.19 Megabytes
    - Green Rubber Gloves, 2021 June 8; UA256.000195; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.25 Megabytes
  - Daugherty, Kevin, circa 2021; UA256.000196
    - The Right Stuff, circa 2021; UA256.000197
      Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Davis, James L., III, circa 2021; UA256.000198; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - The Things I Miss About Being Free, 2021 May 27; UA256.000199; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.21 Megabytes
    - Sounds Like Justice, circa 2021; UA256.000200
    - a Poem for Melba Pattillo, circa 2021; UA256.000201
  - Davis, John L., 2021 July 21; UA256.000202; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Solitude, 2021 July 21; UA256.000203
  - Day, Kenny, 2021 June 20; UA256.000204; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Institutionalized eyes, 2021 June 20; UA256.000205; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.37 Megabytes
  - DeBritto, Timothy, 2021 June 22; UA256.000206; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Inception, 2021 June 22; UA256.000207; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.15 Megabytes
  - Ali Moseley, 2020 November 24 -- 2021 September 14; UA256.000208; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Beyond the Surface, 2020 November 24; UA256.000209
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Dennis, Victoria, 2021 May 17 -- 2021 October 6; UA256.000210; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - The Twelve, 2021 May 17; UA256.000211
    - Do You?, 2021 May 17; UA256.000212
    - Wake Up, 2021 May 17; UA256.000213
  - Dikeos, Rees, 2021 March 29; UA256.000214; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - The Other Side of the Fence, 2021 March 29; UA256.000215; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.34 Megabytes
      Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Dorsey, Leroy, 2021 June 25; UA256.000216; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - An Honest Critique, 2021 June 25; UA256.000217; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.51 Megabytes
      Rhode Island; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Dorsey, Mary, 2021 May 20; UA256.000218
    - Changing the Future, 2021 May 20; UA256.000219
  - Dotson, Michael, circa 2021; UA256.000220
    - Blue, circa 2021; UA256.000221
  - Eggleston, Michael, 2021 May 16; UA256.000222; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    South Carolina; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Life Plus Twenty Five, 2021 May 16; UA256.000223
      South Carolina; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Lil Fire, 2021 May 16; UA256.000224
    - Chasing the Wind, 2021 May 16; UA256.000225
    - Kirkland Cats, 2021 May 16; UA256.000226
    - I love you poetry, 2021 May 16; UA256.000227
    - From the Worst, to the Best, 2021 May 16; UA256.000228; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.50 Megabytes
      South Carolina; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Nipsey Hussle portrait, 2021 May 16; UA256.000229
      South Carolina; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
    - Underpass visual art, 2021 May 16; UA256.000230
    - Self portrait, 2021 May 16; UA256.000231
  - Ehler, Guy Friday, 2021 June 1; UA256.000232; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Proud to Serve, 2021 June 1; UA256.000233
    - Wars end, 2021 June 1; UA256.000234
  - Ehlers, Anthony, 2021 May 11; UA256.000235; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - It all comes round, 2021 May 11; UA256.000236
    - Grief, 2021 May 11; UA256.000237
    - I dug some graves, 2021 May 11; UA256.000238
    - Gods and monsters, 2021 May 11; UA256.000239
    - Why did I stay?, 2021 May 11; UA256.000240
  - Elias, Craig, 2021 June 7 -- 2021 September 10; UA256.000241; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Reeds, Candles, Justice, and Jesus, 2021 June 7; UA256.000242; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.62 Megabytes
      Pennsylvania; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays